[Music] here is an opportunity to manifest what you want in your life satguru offers this powerful
kalpa vriksha meditation this meditation will help you to harness the creative power of the
life energy that is the basis of creation within you before we begin it is important that you
create a Clear Vision or image of what you want in your mind before you start working towards it
take a minute to think about and visualize your goals for the next two to three months
two to three years and your long-term goal or your lifetime achievement
visualize your goals and Visions clearly and in a positive manner see if that is what you really
want your top priority should be your long-term
Vision in such a way that it includes everyone
for example if you want health don't ask for health just for yourself ask for a healthy world
visualize your short-term goal and vision for the next two to three months
visualize your midterm goal and vision for the next two to three years
visualize your long-term goal or lifetime achievement
take a minute to articulate and visualize these goals please close your eyes if you need more time
please press pause and continue whenever you are ready
sit with your hands and legs uncrossed backs rested head should not be rested
keep your hands upon your thighs Palms facing upward your feet slightly apart uncrossed
those of you wearing glasses please keep them aside
please close your eyes meditation
this meditation will help you to harness the creative power
of the life energy that is the basis of creation within you
sit with your hands and legs uncrossed back rested head should not be rested
keep your hands upon your thighs Palms facing upward your feet slightly apart and crossed
take a deep breath and as you exhale relax into it
take another deep breath and as you exhale relax even more into it [Music]
take one more deep breath this time the relaxation should be total foreign
yourself standing in a garden [Music] feel the grass under your bare feet
see what is around you feel all the sensations the Sun the breeze
feel all the sensations of standing there in the garden all by yourself [Music]
please now see that your body is becoming lighter and lighter
feel the lightness spreading through your body [Music]
your body is becoming very very light [Music]
it is becoming so light that slowly you're lifting off the ground
you are beginning to float [Music] you're about six inches above the ground floating
slowly [Music] you are moving upward
you are two feet above the ground
you are moving further upward
you are five feet above the ground
see how it feels all the sensations you are floating five feet above the ground foreign
you are moving further up you are 10 feet above the ground look down and see how everything seems
feel everything around you the breeze the
Sun the sounds and the smells feel everything
you are 10 feet above the ground floating
now you're moving further upward
20 feet above the ground see how it feels [Music]
you are moving further up 50 feet above the ground [Music]
look down and see [Music] how the garden that you just took off from looks [Music]
how the buildings around look the trees the plants the people on the street see
how everything seems to you 50 feet above the ground floating
[Music]
now you have moved 100 feet above the ground look down and see how it feels
see how the buildings are how the people are how the trees and everything else is
how everything seems being
100 feet above the ground
you are moving further up you are reaching towards 200 feet look down and see how
everything seems from this height foreign feel all the sensations the coolness of the breeze
the sunlight and all the other Sensations are floating 200 feet above the ground
look around and see how everything seems floating 200 feet above the ground [Music]
you are moving further upward you are 500 feet above the ground
see how it feels all the sensations
look around and see how the whole town seems when you're 500 feet above the ground floating [Music]
you're going further up one thousand feet see how it feels
look around and see as far as you can see how everything seems floating one
thousand feet above the ground [Music]
now you're moving up very quick five thousand feet see how it feels look around and see
feel the sensations the coolness of the breeze the clouds
and everything else see how it feels floating five thousand feet above the ground [Music]
you are among the clouds now beginning to move horizontally moving
flying through the space
see how everything feels feel the wind on your face [Music]
now you're moving through the space very rapidly five thousand feet above the ground [Music]
you have gone far away from where you started
[Music] traveled far away from where you started
look down and see what is beneath you from five thousand feet above the ground
the terrain is changing rapidly [Music]
you are moving over a very dense forest
foreign [Music] a dense forest beneath you stretched in all directions [Music]
now you have reached a point where in every
direction that you see you see only a dense forest cow
foreign [Music] you see a thick forest cover beneath you stretched in all directions
[Music]
now slowly you are coming down
four thousand feet see how it feels
[Music]
three thousand feet
[Music] two thousand feet [Music]
one thousand feet [Music] now you see a small clearing in the middle of this dense forest
[Music]
500 feet [Music] 200 feet
100 feet see how everything feels
[Music] the forest this little clearing
you're slowly dropping towards that small clearing foreign
[Music]
you notice a small lovely Cottage [Music]
20 feet
you see the cottage clearly now in this small clearing in the middle of the dense forest [Music]
10 feet [Music]
five feet
much closer to the ground [Music]
just two feet above the ground
slowly your feet your bare feet
on touching the ground [Music]
feel all the sensations of being here in a small clearing within this dense forest
[Music]
and you look at this lovely little cottage which has a certain quality about it [Music]
you hear the sounds of the forest [Music] things you smell the fragrance of the forest
above all you are drawn by a certain power
that this little cottage exudes
somehow you're drawn towards this Cottage
slowly start walking towards this lovely Cottage
[Music]
where's it
[Music] feel all the sensations
you are slowly walking towards this lovely little
cottage in this small clearing in the middle of a dense forest
oh [Music] now you're near the door of this Cottage it is not [Music]
slowly Push the door open [Music] you enter the cottage [Music]
as you wish gets adjusted to the dim-lit interior
of the cottage you see your spiritual
Master sitting there on a small pedestal
you see your spiritual Master sitting there on a small pedestal foreign
[Music]
foreign [Music]
gesture
you sit down in front of him in a cross-leg posture [Music]
I feel the Master's presence
oh [Music]
a brilliant sun-like spot appears in your
Master's forehead and a powerful beam of
light strikes you in your forehead and enters you and begins to spread
[Music] it is slowly filling your head
moving towards your throat
moving down the neck
into your shoulders [Music]
and down into your chest and arms [Music] and all the way down to your fingertips
and onto your stomach
the low back region
down into your lower belly hips and onto your thighs
down into your knees further down and all the way down to your toes
[Music]
you are completely filled with this wonderful pure light of his grace foreign
you are completely filled with this wonderful pure light of his grace [Music]
with the source of creation within you ignited and now you are a powerful source of creation
with the source of creation within you ignited you are a powerful source of creation
along with his energies and Grace you can create what you want effortlessly [Music]
along with his energies and Grace you can create what you want effortlessly
now visualize three things that you want to accomplish [Music] one short-term vision
something that you want to accomplish within the next two months
and then a midterm vision something that you want to accomplish in the next two to three years
and then a long-term vision something that you want as a life's accomplishment
now visualize your first division
create a vivid positive image of your vision in your mind [Music]
and see it being accomplished
[Music]
hold the image and see how it feels to have your vision accomplished [Music]
now express your gratitude to your master for having fulfilled your vision [Music]
now visualize your second vision
create a vivid positive image of your vision in your mind
and see it being accomplished [Music]
hold the image see how it feels to have your vision accomplished [Music]
now express your gratitude to your master for having fulfilled your vision [Music]
visualize your third vision
create a vivid positive image of your vision in your mind see it being accomplished [Music]
hold the image and see how it feels to have your vision accomplished [Music]
now express your gratitude to your master for having fulfilled your vision [Applause] [Music]
now reinforce the image of your Visions in your mind
visualize your first Vision in your mind once again
[Music]
see that it is accomplished
visualize the second vision your mind
[Music] and see that it is accomplished
[Music]
now visualize the third vision and see that also is accomplished
now bow down and express your gratitude to your spiritual Master for his grace and energy
[Music]
feel the Delight of being in his presence
it is time to leave slowly come out of the cottage into the bright light [Music]
into the small clearing in the forest
slowly move to the center of this small clearing in the forest feel all the sensations
feel the smells and sounds of the forest [Music]
mind your body has become very light
so light that slowly your body is losing contact with the ground on which you stand
and you are beginning to float
two feet above the ground
further up five feet above the ground see how it feels
[Music] further up
you are 10 feet above the ground
20 feet
[Music] 50 feet see how it feels look down and see the clearing the cottage the forest
100 feet above the ground see how it feels [Music]
further ah
500 feet
[Music] one thousand feet above the ground foreign
feet see how it feels look down and see that small cottage in the middle of the forest
that clearing that Cottage and the powerful presence of your spiritual master [Music]
now you're moving up very rapidly
[Music] five thousand feet
and now you start moving horizontally slowly through the clouds
feel every sensation created by this moment the
breeze the coolness of the priests the sunlight [Music]
you are moving quite rapidly
in a few moments you have come back
to the place where you started
and you're slowly descending
four thousand feet
three thousand feet
two thousand feet
[Music] one thousand feet [Music] 500 feet
you are slowly descending towards the garden where you started
see how it feels
200 feet
100 feet 50. 20. further down
10. five two now very close
and your feet are touching the ground [Music] now you are back in the garden [Music]
you are a powerful being now with the grace and the power of your spiritual master
you are a powerful being now with the source of creation ignited within you
you are a powerful being with the ability to create what you want [Music]
take your own time take your own time slowly very slowly open your eyes
[Music]
dear
[Music] [Applause]
[Music]
meaning [Laughter] [Music]
foreign
[Music]
[Music] [Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
foreign [Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music]
foreign [Music] [Applause] [Music]
foreign
[Music]
[Music] [Applause] [Music]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause] [Music]
thank you [Music]